myth-weavers.com 2019-06-23

# Privacy policy - Myth-Wiki

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at weaver@myth-weavers.com. 

At www.myth-weavers.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by www.myth-weavers.com and how that information is used. 

###  The Public and Collaborative Nature of the Projects 

All Projects of the Myth-Weavers are collaboratively developed by its users using the MediaWiki software. Anyone with Internet access (and not otherwise restricted from doing so) may edit the publicly editable pages of these sites with or without logging in as a registered user. By doing this, editors create a published document, and a public record of every word added, subtracted, or changed. This is a public act, and editors are identified publicly as the author of such changes. All contributions made to a Project, and all publicly available information about those contributions, are irrevocably licensed and may be freely copied, quoted, reused and adapted by third parties with few restrictions. 

###  Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.myth-weavers.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

###  Cookies and Web Beacons

www.myth-weavers.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user accesses or visits, and customize Web page content based on the visitor's browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

###  DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.myth-weavers.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visits to www.myth-weavers.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

###  Advertising

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include the following. 

  * Google Adsense 
  * Amazon 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send the advertisements and links that appear on www.myth-weavers.com directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.myth-weavers.com has no access to or control over the cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.myth-weavers.com's privacy policy does not apply to such other advertisers or web sites, as we cannot control their activities. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

##  Disclaimer 

Myth-Weavers believes that maintaining and preserving the privacy of user data is an important value. This Privacy Policy, together with other policies, resolutions, and actions by Myth-Weavers, represents a committed effort to safeguard the security of the limited user information that is collected and retained on our servers. Nevertheless, Myth-Weavers cannot guarantee that user information will remain private. We acknowledge that, in spite of our committed effort to protect private user information, determined individuals may still develop data-mining and other methods to uncover such information and disclose it. For this reason, Myth-Weavers can make no guarantee against unauthorized access to information provided in the course of participating in Myth-Weavers projects or related communities. 

    If you would like to request a change to this page, please contact a staff member.
